module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What unrefined element is the fictional element Vibranium, from Black Panther, based on?', 
    a: 'Coltan',
    b: 'Chromium',
    c: 'Mercury',
    d: 'Cadmium',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What type of wood is most used to make pencils?', 
    a: 'Pine',
    b: 'Balsa',
    c: 'Cedar',
    d: 'Beech',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What are the concrete walls separating traffic on highways called?', 
    a: 'New York dividers',
    b: 'Jersey barriers',
    c: 'Chicago splitters',
    d: 'Border walls',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who invented the JavaScript programming language?', 
    a: 'Troy Acosta',
    b: 'Bill Gates',
    c: 'Brendan Eich',
    d: 'Steve Ballmer',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who owns the 7UP brand in the US?', 
    a: 'Pepsi Co',
    b: 'CocaCola',
    c: 'Kuerig Dr. Pepper',
    d: 'Nestle',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was Nic Cage\'s first movie?', 
    a: 'Raising Arizona',
    b: 'Valley Girl',
    c: 'Moonstruck',
    d: 'Fast Times at Ridgemont High',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who wrote Jingle Bells?', 
    a: 'Jim from the Office',
    b: 'James Lord Pierpont',
    c: 'James Summers',
    d: 'James Pachelbel',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What # is the new conference room in HQ2(Pandora)?', 
    a: 'CR8',
    b: 'CR9',
    c: 'CR10',
    d: 'John C Reilly',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many nights does Hanukkah last?', 
    a: '7',
    b: '8',
    c: '2',
    d: '12',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does auld lang syne mean?', 
    a: 'The good old days',
    b: 'Happy days',
    c: 'Old language Sign',
    d: 'Times long past',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];